Crap!
I forgot my sleepover
supplies at Yukiya's place.
She went to the convenience store the day they decided on the sleepover.
N-Now what?!
Where did I leave it?
I went all-out preparing that stuff...
What if Yukiya's parents see?
Hee
hee
Sheesh, Miku-chan.
You know exactly what to do, huh?
I shouldn't have put so much
obvious effort into it!
This is so embarrassing!
What's up?
Yukiya?
I think I forgot my
toothbrush set over there.
Oh, yeah, I found it.
It was in the bathroom,
so I brought it to my room.
What a relief.
Miku
Connected
What'll you do?
Do you want to leave this here?
I mean, you know, you used to
leave this sort of stuff here,
so I figure, y'know.
Well, I don't have a use for it at home.
I guess I'll keep it there.
As long as you don't mind.
Okay.
Got it.
Oh, but Yukiya...
You better not use my toothbrush.
Huh?!
Why would anyone do that? Gross.
A cute girl used that
toothbrush, you know.
You know?!
Seriously, shut up.
I Want to End This Love Game
Episode 8
My Childhood Friend and the Student Council President
Miku-chan.
What brings you here
so early in the morning?
Onii's still asleep.
I know. Sorry.
I knew I might be bothering you, but...
Oh, hey, morning, Miku-chan.
You're here early.
Good morning.
Miku-chan, do you want to
go wake up Yuki-chan?
Really?
I've always thought about
doing something like that.
I know, right?
Go get him.
Thanks for having me.
Waka-chan, is there something
happening between those two?
So, so much.
I don't even want jam for breakfast.
I've always had this plan in mind,
even though I haven't
had a chance to do it
since I haven't been over in a while.
But after what happened...
I can do it.
What guy could resist his cute
childhood friend coming to wake him up?
I never went into his room back then.
H-He's so cute!
Aww, he looks like a
baby when he's sleeping.
Look, he had snacks!
Jagabee
Yukiya's room really smells like him.
Miku?
Why are you here?!
Bones'
Friend
Milk
Beverage
Why are you in your underwear?!
Ooh.
I'm off.
Here.
Let's go together.
I see what you're up to.
What's wrong?
Did that get your heart racing,
locking arms with me?
That's not it!
It's not that.
I was just worried that you might get wet.
What's the matter?
Heart skip a beat?
N-Not at all.
I'm so stuffy from
the humidity and body heat.
Her skin seems different from
usual because of the rain.
I sweat a lot.
I'm worried I might be sticky.
I'm totally touching her there!
Is she okay with this? She is, right?
Miku!
Asagi-kun!
Morning!
Nacchan!
M-Morning!
Asagi-kun!
Guess what?
Miku says...
She'd rather be under your umbr—
I can't hear her.
"I wanted to come back so that
Nacchan doesn't get wet," huh?
Once the rainy season ends,
summer begins.
This is the summer...
m 0 0 l 0 57.999 l 276.999 69.999 l 276.999 3
School Assembly
Now, a word on club activities
during the summer.
It'll be hot during the day.
Don't forget to stay hydrated,
and don't push yourself past your limit.
Summer break, huh...
There's so much I want to do with Miku.
Surefire Victory
But...
Too much of a loner to have any idea of what people do in the summer
I'm not there yet.
I need to become a better man
for Miku than anyone else.
I need to get there by summer break.
Seki-sensei.
m 942.999 716.001 l 942 819.999 l 1203.999 819 l 1203 714.999
Was sleeping
I'm sure you're tired,
but please understand that you need
to be a role model for the students.
My bad.
My bad
Please keep it
together.
Please keep it together.
That scared me!
I thought I got yelled at.
Isn't it crazy how she can
scold a teacher like that?
Yeah.
Pardon me.
Moving on, things to be mindful
of during summer break...
I used to be in middle school with her.
She had the nickname Blood-Soaked Lily.
Apparently she beat up a guy, broke
his nose, and sent him to the hospital.
Actually? Yikes.
She doesn't look that bad, though.
Oh, it isn't that she's
a delinquent or anything.
The story was that she was helping
a friend who was getting bullied.
She's badass, charismatic,
collected, and pretty.
She's popular with both girls and boys.
Huh.
Please have a meaningful,
productive summer
and prepare well for the new semester.
Boof!
Hey, you were looking in my direction
during the school assembly.
After all the time we spent
together in the morning, too.
Did you miss me already?
H-Hey, what? What?
Rooftop Field
Rooftop
No
Entry
Okay, but I saw you winking.
You were trying to get
my attention, weren't you?
No one will come up here.
I could stare at you forever.
Y-Yukiya...
What are we doing here?
What's the matter?
Feeling shy now?
That's not the point.
What if someone sees us?
It's fine.
No one will find us here.
S-Student Council President!
I Want to End This Love Game
What are you two doing here?
It doesn't look like anything appropriate
for someone on their way home.
tremble...      tremble
U-Um...
I-It isn't what you think.
We're childhood friends,
and this is just us playing around.
Rooftop Field
Rooftop
No
Entry
I know.
You're playing some
silly game, aren't you?
The Love Game, was it?
Why does she know?
It should only be my uncle,
Hinako-san, and maybe Nacchan...
I'm the student council president.
I keep a close eye on
everything going on in school.
When you were eating lunch together,
when you were half way up the stairs,
when you were in the library,
this morning, on your way to school...
I've seen you every time.
Is that even part
of the student council president's job?
I'll have you tell me all about
this matter tomorrow.
Come to the student council
office during lunchtime.
Understood?
Y-Yes!
Scary!
It's your fault for being thoughtless
about when you make your moves!
That's exactly your problem!
What do we do?
We're going to get lectured tomorrow.
It'll be fine.
It was my fault for starting it.
I'll protect you no matter
what she says.
No, I got carried away, too.
I can't let you take all the heat.
Really? You were so freaked out.
There, there, that was scawy, wasn't it?
Don't worry, you'll be okay.
You're so annoying!
Nice batting!
Childhood friends...
m 1332.999 359.001 l 1332.999 420 l 1490.001 420 l 1490.001 359.001
Student Council Room
m 470.001 414.999 l 470.001 666 l 1383 660 l 1383 414.999
Getting right to it, about yesterday...
Love Game Investigation
April 8 – June 12
Shinju High School Student Council
You two aren't even
in a relationship, are you?
You aren't even dating, and yet you're
exhibiting so much affection at school.
Unbelievable.
Obscene!
Sh-Shirayuri-senpai, I was
the one who started this game.
I'm the one to blame.
No, I was being forceful yesterday, so...
No, I was...
No, no, I was...
Don't you find that,
being childhood friends,
you tend to treat each other like family?
Which is all the more why,
once you come of age,
you become shy about
playing with each other.
Or they might shout your first name at
school and give people the wrong idea.
You really want to talk to them,
but you end up putting even
more space between you and them.
I think that's what happens
between most childhood friends.
W-Well...
Wait, we're here
to get scolded, aren't we?
Don't her examples seem oddly specific?
Hey, Kazane, you're here.
Oh, were you busy?
What? Could we deal with it later?
Oh, no, don't mind me.
Sorry,
one sec
Hey, what are you doing?
Well, you said you were taking this
to the staff office, didn't you?
I thought it might be heavy for you.
Don't insult me.
I can deal with this myself.
You're clearly in the middle of something!
Come on.
You're busy with your student
council president work.
Just let me handle all the grunt work.
I want to be useful to you.
Fine, you're right.
You're such a meathead, Kakeru.
That's about the only thing
I could let you handle.
Exactly.
This is my jam, so depend on me lots.
Never mind that. Kakeru.
You finally have some time, so why
don't you do what you want to be doing?
That's why I'm here to help you out.
You had something on your head.
Seriously!
Don't I always tell you not to
come into my personal space?!
A good punch, as always.
I'm about the only one who can
stand your punches, aren't I?
Shut up!
Get going to the staff
office already! Thank you!
Okay, okay.
Don't be too mean to the first years.
Shirayuri-senpai...
He's your childhood friend, isn't he?
After all that fierce talk about
us being obscene and stuff...
Senpai...
That's right.
He's my childhood friend.
We've lived next to each other
since we were in preschool.
I don't even remember why anymore,
but I've always...
But he's been all about
baseball since we were little.
Meanwhile, you saw how crude I am.
And I'm quick to resort to violence.
I beat the snot out of a guy
in middle school,
Gloom
and people started
calling me blood-soaked.
So that actually happened.
Kakeru doesn't think anything of me.
Which is why...
Which is why he has no trouble
acting like that toward me!
That stupid nice guy!
T-True, it would suck
having that happen to you
and he doesn't even realize it.
It's like they're playing
the Love Game without even trying.
He keeps making my heart
skip a beat all the time.
I can't stand it!
I want to make his heart stop.
I mean, you'd have
killed him at that point.
It's a figure of speech.
Meaning you want to get his heart racing
so hard he can't even breathe, right?
Sigh...
I was just trying to lighten the mood...
I know how you feel, Senpai.
If I can be of any help,
I'd be happy to hear you out.
Fine.
Teach me how to play the Love Game.
Th-There's something in your hair.
Th-Thanks.
Amazing.
Too amazing!
How can you even do that?!
Just imagining myself
doing that kills me!
It's too obscene!
I-Is that obscene?
But it only works because
you're cute, Sakura-san.
I couldn't pull it off.
What are you talking about?
You're doing all you can
for the guy you like.
How is that not cute?
Well?
Did that get your heart going?
She might make us play the game
forever if I deny it now.
It did.
I see.
Right.
So that's the kind of thing boys like.
I don't know, though...
Can I really make it work?
She must really love him.
Love Game Investigation
April 8 – June 12
Shinju High School Student Council
Smile.
The trick to winning is to smile.
Any guy would appreciate seeing
someone give them a genuine smile.
Smile...
Got it. I'll do my best.
That was rare.
You never have the
guts to talk to girls.
Why? I always do.
Which means you've been getting jolts
every time I smiled at you, then.
Don't be dumb.
She seems so much more
well put-together than I am.
I can't!
But even she has to
work hard at some things.
Next Time
My Childhood Friend Becomes My Apprentice?
Er, Wakana here.
Next episode of I Want
to End This Love Game:
"My Childhood Friend
Becomes My Apprentice?"